export const data = [
    {
        question: "What is the function of a pacemaker?",
        option1: "Controls heartbeats",
        option2: "Constrols respiration",
        option3: "Controls toxicity in blood",
        option4: "Controls muscles action",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "When do spring rides occur?",
        option1: "Only in the spring",
        option2: "When the Sun, Earth, and Moon don't align",
        option3: "When the Sun, Earth, and Moon are aligned",
        option4: "None of the above",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the chess term for a drawn game?",
        option1: "A draw",
        option2: "A dead heat",
        option3: "A cold castle",
        option4: "Stalemate",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Originating from WWII, the phrase 'being Switzerland' means what?",
        option1: "Being sneaky",
        option2: "Being neutral",
        option3: "Being fast",
        option4: "Being old",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Mexican Beach Resort is not on its West Coast?",
        option1: "Cancun",
        option2: "Acapulco",
        option3: "Puerto Vallarta",
        option4: "Mazatlan",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "In Shakespeare's The Taming of the Shrew, who tames the Shrew?",
        option1: "Othello",
        option2: "Petruchio",
        option3: "Hamlet",
        option4: "Benvolio",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the main Character in Les Miserables written by Victor Hugo?",
        option1: "Marius",
        option2: "Hugh Jackman",
        option3: "Eponine",
        option4: "Jean Valjean",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "The first international cricket match was in what year?",
        option1: "1966",
        option2: "1844",
        option3: "1799",
        option4: "2000",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a conductor use when leading an orchestra?",
        option1: "The Score and a Baton",
        option2: "The Stanza and a Baton",
        option3: "A Measure and a Stick",
        option4: "The Overture and a Wand",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What was Michael J Fox's characters name in the movie 'Back to the Future'?",
        option1: "Marty",
        option2: "Calvin",
        option3: "George",
        option4: "Biff",
        ans: 1,
    },
    
]